Hello?
Oh, hey, Julia.
I was just on my way over.
Anything I need to bring?
Thai food? Wine? Batteries?
What do you mean, don't come?
Gee, do you really think your psychiatrist
is the best judge of who you sleep with?
Well, sure you could do better.
We could both do better.
But in the meantime,
I am on my way over.
Okay, okay, need to stop you here.
There is a big difference between
"meaningless" and "degrading. "
You know what? I think
we'll just have to agree to disagree.
Okay, then, you have a nice life too.
Why do these women insist
on getting well?
- Hey, Alan...
- Hang on, Charlie.
This is an important moment...
...and I wanna savor it.
Alan J...
...Harper.
What's the big deal?
It's just an alimony check.
Not an alimony check.
This is my final alimony check.
Isn't it beautiful?
Oh, right,
Judith is getting married this weekend.
Exactly.
And you know what that means.
You can finally
kick in a few bucks around here?
Good one. No.
It means Alan gets new underwear.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go pick up my son...
...and deliver this last drop of blood money
to the former Mrs. Alan Harper...
...and soon to be Mrs. Herb Melnick.
May God have mercy on his soul.
Amen.
- So you want some company?
- You wanna come with me?
Yeah, why not? I don't have any plans.
You got stood up again, didn't you?
I'm starting to think all these girls
have the same damn shrink.
If you're gonna come,
grab your camera.
You can take some snapshots
of Pharaoh Judith letting her Alan go.
Got the camera right here.
- You carry it with you?
- Thought I had a date.
Takes video too.
I hand it to you, Charlie.
Stopping at the copy place
was a great idea.
And the picture will make
a terrific Christmas card.
Wanna get the door, Herb?
Stop yelling at me!
I am not yelling. This is yelling!
You know what?
This really isn't that funny.
- Oh, hi, Alan, Charlie.
- Herb.
- Hey.
- Is this a bad time?
The Spanish Inquisition was a bad time.
This is hell.
Come on in.
So, what's going on?
A little pre-wedding jitters?
We could call it that,
but we'd just be sugarcoating hell.
Oh, don't worry. As soon as Judith puts
on that beautiful white gown...
...marches down the aisle...
- She doesn't want white.
Says it makes her look fat.
Oh, well, that's nice.
She wants to look
trim and fit for the honeymoon.
You're sugarcoating hell again, Alan.
You wanna help the guy?
Stop talking and smother him with a pillow.
- Oh, great.
- Hey, there's the blushing bride.
She doesn't look fat at all.
- Go ahead, give her the check.
- What check?
Oh, well,
I figured as long as I was here...
...that I would give you
your last and final alimony check.
Got it.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Just a little souvenir.
I'll go find Jake.
She's being a good sport.
Let's get the big check.
No, forget the big check.
Forget the big check.
So, you know,
I read an interesting story the other day.
Married men live, on average,
10 years longer than single men.
What if they don't want to?
Come on, you and Judith
were meant for each other.
- What could possibly come between you?
- My sister.
- You got a sister?
- Down, Charlie.
She came out to help with the wedding,
but it's not really helping.
- What's she look like?
- Charlie.
- She doesn't have a therapist, does she?
- I swear to God.
So, what do you think?
Should I wear it
or have a vet check it for worms?
No, no, it looks fine.
- Myra, this is Judith's first husband Alan.
- Hi.
So how does this work?
Do you get your original testicles back...
...or does my brother give you his?
Myra, the castration jokes
are getting a little old.
Not at my house.
- This is Alars brother, Charlie.
- Oh, yeah, the booze-riddled sleazebag.
She did not hear that from me.
That's okay.
Not like it's a big secret.
Myra, where the hell is Jake?
- How should I know?
- I asked you to get him ready for his father.
You also asked me
to try on this satin stool sample.
Herb, tell your sister it's a lovely dress.
Herb, tell your fiancée the diet pills
are affecting her judgment, but not her ass.
That's it. She's gotta go.
- I can't throw out family.
- And that's the bitch of it, Herb.
Hey, you know, Charlie and I
were thinking of taking Jake out to a movie.
- We were?
- We were.
- Myra, would you like to join us?
- You didn't say anything about a movie.
I wanted to surprise you.
Hey, you know, that's a great idea.
Go to a movie with Alan and Charlie.
Can I wear my pretty new dress?
Get her out, Herb.
Hey, look what I found in the bushes.
God, I hate family movies.
What, you don't buy the central premise
that a dog can play hockey?
Well, not as a power forward.
Oh, we're flying the friendly skies,
are we?
- After you.
- Why, thank you.
Ahh. So you're staying at Judith's.
Yep.
What did she say about me?
Well, if she's telling the truth, we really
shouldn't be drinking out of the same cup.
That might be the nicest thing
she's ever said about me.
I just don't understand
what my brother sees in her.
You know, 15 years ago,
I asked the exact same question.
Little tip?
Don't do it during the wedding toast.
Maybe you can clear something up
for me.
Herb says
you're a successful jingle writer.
But Judith says you are a drunken,
talentless hack...
...who passed out
and fell into a pit of money.
So, what do you need cleared up?
But, ahem, you have me at a disadvantage.
I don't know why Judith hates you.
Hmm... It's hard to say.
Maybe it's because I'm smart.
Maybe it's because I'm independent.
Maybe it's because I offered my brother
a thousand dollars to call off the wedding.
I did the same thing with my brother.
You did?
Well, actually,
it was a thousand-dollar hooker.
But the thought was the same.
So, Myra...
...what do you do?
I teach high school economics.
Huh.
It may sound like a boring life,
but at night...
...I dress up like a giant spider
and fight crime.
Interesting. Now, did you decide spider
and have the costume made...
...or find the costume and say,
"okay, spider"?
Are you mocking the Scarlet Arachnid?
Sorry, sorry.
It's just hard to believe
that you're Herb's sister. He's so...
Hapless?
I was gonna say tall, but hapless works.
To hapless Herb.
To the Scarlet Arachnid.
Shh.
My enemies are everywhere.
BoTH
Let's all go to the lobby
Let's all go to the lobby
Let's all go to the lobby
And have ourselves a treat
We're here.
- Oh, yes. Judith's house of pain.
- Shh, shh, shh.
Lxnay. That's her idkay.
We're here.
Well, thanks for the movie.
- Wait, wait, wait. I'll walk you.
- Why, thank you.
Whoa-oh!
You okay?
I never know till I sober up.
- I think they like each other.
- Sure, they like each other.
No, I mean they "like" like each other.
Oh, no, Jake. Your Uncle Charlie only
"like" likes a certain type of woman.
- Mom calls them tramps.
- Well...
That's as good a word as any.
Thanks. That was fun.
Yeah, it was.
See you around.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I don't know why I did that.
Who cares?
Looks like Aunt Myra's a tramp, huh?
Oh, come on, Judith,
so he gave her a kiss.
It's no big deal.
Yeah, that's how Charlie says goodbye.
Yep, some people shake hands,
some people wave.
My brother darts his tongue
in and out of your mouth.
- What did I miss?
- You know Dr. Melnick?
The guy your mom's marrying?
- He has a sister...
- Got it.
I'm sure it has nothing to do
with you, Judith.
Wait, hang on a second.
- Are you done with your breakfast?
- Yeah.
- Then get out.
- Fine.
- Berta will just tell me later, right?
- Right.
Okay, Judith, that's insane.
Charlie would not do
Myra just to piss you off.
I don't think.
How would I know what he sees in her?
She got working girl-parts?
You know what, you leave.
Send Jake back.
Okay, okay, fine, fine, I'll talk to him.
I don't know.
I'll tell him to keep his hands off Myra.
And then I'll tell the rain not to fall...
...the Earth not to spin,
and you to stop nagging me.
Oh, boy, I'm gonna pay for that.
You know what your problem is?
Phone cojones.
- Excuse me?
- When you're on the phone with her...
...you got boulders between your legs.
The minute you hang up
you're as smooth as a Ken doll.
Phone cojones.
Good to have a name for it.
So tell me about the sister.
I don't know.
She doesn't seem like his type.
What, no coin slot in her forehead?
- Morning.
Morning.
Charlie, we need to talk about Myra.
- Yeah, that was probably a mistake.
- It was?
She's a nice kid,
but she's just not, you know...
A red-hot simpleton with no self-respect?
I hope she didn't take
that kiss thing too seriously.
- So you're not planning on pursuing her?
- No, no, no.
In fact, I got a date tonight
with a lovely sex addict...
...whose therapist is on vacation.
It's what we eligible bachelors call
"a window of opportunity. "
You know, there's a special section
in hell reserved for people like you.
That's good because I'd hate
to have to stand on line.
So I'm like, "Yeah, I can make
a lot of money as a lingerie model...
...but then who's gonna take me
seriously as a director?"
- Good point.
- Sometimes I wish I wasrt beautiful.
I mean, ugly people have it
so easy, you know?
- I've heard.
- So, what about you?
- Still writing jingles?
- Just during the day.
At night I dress up as a big spider
and fight crime.
Huh. You know, I dated a cop once.
Well, it wasrt so much a date
as a way to get out of a ticket. Heh.
Interesting.
- Okay, here we are.
- Oh, I hope this place has fresh lobster.
That frozen stuff is just disgusting.
You know what, Herb?
Forget it, I'll do it myself.
I said I would do it, I'll do it.
Ugh. For God's sake, Judith,
get off his back.
No one's talking to you, Myra.
Okay, everyone calm down.
I'm doing it.
- Oh, hi, Charlie.
- Hi, Herb.
Just taking out the trash.
Yeah, I'm coming
from doing the same thing.
Great, he leaves the door wide o...
What the hell are you doing here?
That's a good question.
- See, the thing is, I...
- oh, hey, Charlie.
Hi, Myra.
No, no. I forbid it. Not in my house.
What brings you to the cul-de-sac
of the damned?
Just in the neighborhood.
That's nice. Come on in.
Thanks.
I said no. Doesrt anybody listen to me?
I'm doing it, look!
You know, I really didn't expect
to see you again.
- Well, I wasrt doing anything, so...
No, Alan, listen to me.
He's here right now.
Why would I kid about that?
I don't know,
maybe his other date didn't work out.
Ah. The plot thickens.
Okay, okay, I can explain.
No, I can't.
Give it a shot.
Well...
...I was with this girl and I suddenly realized
that I'd rather be with someone...
...who I, you know,
actually enjoy being with.
Oh, just forget it, Alan. You're useless.
Herb, do something.
Hey.
I'm going out for ice cream.
Anyone wanna join me?
Charlie, whers the last time
you had a cone with sprinkles?
You know what, Herb? Judith can relax.
I'm gonna check into a hotel.
Myra, no. You don't have to do that.
Yes, she does.
Hey, she's my sister,
she can stay as long as she wants.
I really appreciate this.
- I'll go get my stuff.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
You don't have to stay at a hotel.
I got room at my place.
- Yeah, I'll bet you do.
- No, no, no.
No strings attached.
- Really?
- Really.
- Still, I couldn't impose like that.
- It's no imposition.
It's a big house.
There's plenty of room.
- You're sure?
- Absolutely.
Okay, then, I'll be right back.
Herb!
You wanna come too?
Are you nuts?
With Myra out of the house,
I might get lucky tonight.
Really? She seems pretty angry.
It's better when she's angry.
Coming, pookie.
This just sucks.
It's for a couple of days
till the wedding.
Yeah, but why does she have to stay
in my room?
Because... I don't know, you're the kid.
Yeah, well, it's not fair.
Yeah, well, get over it.
Oh, my God!
Jake, that's disgusting.
Yeah, well, get over it.
Go to sleep.
Did you brush your teeth?
Dad, I'm asleep.
Go brush your teeth.
- I can't. I don't have my toothbrush.
- Well, go get it.
Man, I have to do everything
around here.
Aunt Myra? I have to get my toothbrush.
Aunt Myra?
Huh.
Oh.
Myra.
- Hi.
- Is everything okay?
- Everything's fine. I just wanted to chat.
Oh, okay.
- I can go if you want.
- No, no. This is fine.
So.
- What's up?
- We never talked about that kiss last night.
Right, right.
That was out of character for me.
Really?
That's not the word on the street.
Okay, let me explain.
With me, kissing is usually
just a prelude to sex.
Last night, sex was the last thing
on my mind.
Oh, gee, what girl
doesn't like to hear that?
No, no, let me finish.
I kissed you because I really liked you.
And I wanted to express my...
...liking of you.
- Be still my beating heart.
Come on, Myra, I drove all the way
to Judith's house to see you.
And you know what's at Judith's house?
Judith.
- That was very brave of you.
- Oh, no, it wasrt brave, it was...
To tell you the truth, I don't know
what it was and I'm not...
...really sure what to do here.
What do you wanna do here?
Let's forget about me for a second.
- What about you?
- What about me?
You kissed first. Why'd you do that?
Oh, I was plowed.
Really?
Oh, come on, you moron.
I'm sitting in the middle of your bed
in my sexiest lingerie.
All right. I'm pretty sure
I know what to do now.
- Charlie?
- Yeah?
I don't wanna put any pressure on you...
...but I'm a virgin.
You are?
Man, you gotta stop sleeping
with dumb girls.
It's rubbing off on you.
Why can't I sleep in my bed?
Aunt Myra's not there.
I'm sure she will be.
She's probably just getting
something in the kitchen.
That's not the kitchen.